reigningchamp.com 2010-09-03

# Reigning Champ Sweaters Hoodies Fleece Jackets Shirts

## Privacy Policy

### Unsubscribe from our newsletter

If you wish to unsubscribe from our subscriber list, simply click on the "unsubscribe" link located at the bottom of each newsletter you received and your email will be promptly taken off from our newsletter system.

CYC Design Corporation ("CYC"), which owns the Reigning Champ brand, shares a strict policy with respect to maintaining the privacy of subscribers to all Reigning Champ special offers, blogs and information services. This Privacy Policy outlines what specific information is gathered on the company's main website and related websites, and how that information is used. Maintaining the privacy of your information is of paramount importance to us as it helps foster confidence, goodwill and stronger relationships with our customers and industry partners. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free contact [info@reigningchamp.com](mailto:info@reigningchamp.com).

### Information Collection and Use

CYC explicitly asks when we need information that personally identifies you ("Personal Information"). Your personal information is used to create your personal record for the purposes of communicating, distributing email, news alerts and/or traditional mail. Demographic and profile data collected by CYC may be used to tailor this web site or any requested email communications, and to display information that is more relevant to you. Under no circumstances will CYC make any personal information about an individual user available to anyone. Your email address is used to only send you information that you have requested by subscribing to the posted information service(s). CYC allows you to elect to receive, or not receive, certain information from CYC. CYC adheres strictly to a permission-based email policy. Except as mentioned above, CYC will not send you unsolicited email information, commercial offers or advertisements. CYC will not sell, rent, or loan our contact lists or our news and/or information subscriber contact lists to any outside firms. All emails that you have requested will have an option to unsubscribe. Unsubscribe requests are fulfilled within minutes and no further communications will be sent to users who have stated that they do not wish to receive the specified information.

### Communications from the Company

We send all new subscribers a welcoming email to verify their email address. Subscribers will occasionally receive information on reigning Champ and other CYC apparel brands, offers, announcements, events, information delivery services, important news, and company newsletters. Out of respect for the privacy of subscribers, we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Users can unsubscribe via the unsubscribe mechanism at the bottom of each email. Also, from time to time, we may include in our own email notices or newsletters, news, offers or announcements by one of our partners in business, but we would never, under any circumstances, share all or part of your contact information with a third party.

### E-News & Mobil Alerts

If a user wishes to subscribe to one or more of our email or Mobil Alert services, we ask for contact information such as name and email address, and when a Mobil Alert is subscribed to, for a SMS-capable telephone number. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications via the unsubscribe mechanism at the bottom of each email.

### Website Usage

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. We do not link your IP address to any personally identifiable information. We use tracking information to determine which areas our site users visit based on traffic to those areas. CYC does not track what individual users read, but rather how often each page is visited. This helps us maintain a superior and informative website for you.

### Security Technology

CYC has adopted the latest server, database, backup and firewall technologies to protect our information assets. These technologies are deployed as part of a sophisticated security architecture. All data resides in a tightly controlled, secure hosted data center. These protocols mean that information about the identity and preferences of individual subscribers is never accessible to anyone outside CYC and its contracted website and mail administration and hosting partners. We are committed to maintaining the security of your personally identifiable information.

### Policy Modifications

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when CYC makes changes to this privacy statement, we will highlight the changes on our homepage and/or email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. However, please be assured that if the Privacy Policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this Privacy Policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this Privacy Policy, without your prior consent.

### Correct Errors In Your Information?

You can access and correct errors in your personally identifiable information by contacting us as indicated below. While CYC uses reasonable efforts to ensure that the information we hold about you is accurate, complete and current, we rely on you to inform us about changes to your contact or other relevant information.

### Contacting Us About Privacy

If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact: [info@reigningchamp.com](mailto:info@reigningchamp.com "email us a ReigningChamp.com")
